You can't play by the rules if there aren't any.
The Corruptor is a action, crime, thriller film directed by James Foley.
Danny is a young cop partnered with Nick, a
seasoned but ethically tainted veteran.
As the two try to stop a gang war in Chinatown, Danny relies on Nick but grows
increasingly uncomfortable with the way Nick gets things done.
Danny Wallace, played by Mark Wahlberg.
Nick Chen, played by Chow Yun-Fat.
Bobby Vu, played by Byron Mann.
Benny Wong, played by Kim Chan.
Henry Lee, played by Ric Young.
Schabacker, played by Paul Ben-Victor.
The Corruptor is a 1999 American action film directed by James Foley.
The film was written by Robert Pucci, and produced by Dan Halsted.
The film stars Chow Yun-fat and Mark Wahlberg.
The film was released in the United States on March 12, 1999.
The film explores themes of new york city, life and
death, police, chinatown, gang war.
The tone is emotional and intense.